Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session one of unit four, it's
time to complete the relevant
section and the assessment booklet.
If you haven't already done so you can use
the assessment link on the final page to
save and download your assessment booklet
in a suitable location on your computer.
Once you've done that, you can then up
in the assessment booklet and begin.
You may also want to have a look at the
hints and tips, which will assist you
when you come to answer the questions.
So assessment booklet 4, if
you scroll down to page 2
and pop your name at the top.
And then we come to section one,
which is know about common and
emerging threats to cyber security.
There is only one question in this
section and this relates to you
providing a description of the common
and emerging threats to cyber security.
So what are the common threats?
So give a description
of those common threats.
But it also asks you to
consider the emerging threats.
So thinking about how we are now
working and the advances in technology
and communications and the tools
and software out there, what are the
emerging threats to cyber security?
So once you're happy with your
answer, proofread your work, make
sure you're happy with everything.
And then save the document
and move on to session two.